{
    "subject": "resource/Nuclear_Rabbit",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Novato,_California",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Nuclear Rabbit is Novato, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8469619154930115,
            "question": "What is the hometown of Nuclear Rabbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8208553194999695,
            "question": "Is Novato, California the birthplace of Nuclear Rabbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5761595964431763,
            "question": "In which state is Novato located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3455166220664978,
            "question": "What is the population of Novato?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29661813378334045,
            "question": "What is known about Nuclear Rabbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2722233831882477,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Novato?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24423003196716309,
            "question": "Where does Nuclear Rabbit call home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22042915225028992,
            "question": "What are some popular attractions in Novato?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19679151475429535,
            "question": "Does Nuclear Rabbit live in a house or a burrow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04932142049074173,
            "question": "Are there any other fictional characters from California?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Nuclear Rabbit is Novato, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5903_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Nuclear Rabbit live in a house or a burrow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5903_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular attractions in Novato?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5903_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Nuclear Rabbit call home?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5903_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5903_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents mention that Nuclear Rabbit was started in Novato, California. Therefore, the statement that the hometown of Nuclear Rabbit is Novato, California, is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}